# Teanna Tang

## **UX/UI** Designer

#### Contact



Baltimore, MD 410-530-1312

□ tangteanna@gmail.com



#### **Skills**

User Research and User Testing Creating User Personas **User Flows** Wireframing and Prototyping User Interface Design Information Architecture Style Guides

#### Tools

Sketch **Figma** Adobe XD Balsamiq Marvel HTML CSS JavaScript

## **Education**

Feb 2022 - May 2022 Frontend Development Certificate CareerFoundry UX Design Program

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022 **UX Design Certificate** CareerFoundry UX Design Program

Aug 2016 - May 2020 **BS** Degree in Animal Sciences University of Maryland, College Park

#### **Profile**

Passionate UX Designer with experience in research and user-centered design. Skilled in creating wireframes and prototypes with tools such as Sketch, Figma, and Adobe XD. Comfortable working collaboratively or crossfunctionally to identify problems and design creative solutions.

### **Projects**

Sept 2021 - Present

PlutoPay, Virtual Wallet App / CareerFoundry Case Study

- Applied a user-centered design process to design a responsive web app for online shopping and making online transactions
- Created interactive prototype with Adobe XD
  - https://xd.adobe.com/view/bbdacf12-1b64-4f05-94e8d2ebfee1c4d8-ee89/
- Case Study:
  - https://www.behance.net/gallery/135860833/PlutoPay

Aug 2021 - Sept 2021

Study Buddies, Flashcard App/CareerFoundry Case Study

- Conducted user interviews and surveys to gather research data to develop user personas, sitemaps, and user flows
- Created mid-fidelity wireframes with Figma:
  - https://www.figma.com/community/file/1091926616991 630583/Study-Buddies

## Experience

2021 - Present

#### Dance Instructor/JAMZ Dance Studio

- Worked with many students with a variety of ages and skill levels
- Communicated with parents and staff to ensure all expectations and goals were met

2018 - 2020

#### Lab Researcher/Matrix Laboratories

- Conducted various research projects with laboratory team
- Collected project data
- Investigated problematic cases using effective communication with administration team